<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Wildfire]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Wildfire]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/wildfire/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2016 02:08:42 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/wildfire/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What is Wildfire?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>What is Wildfire?</h1><h2>The word "wildfire" was burned into my being in April of 2015. I knew God was preparing me for my year of wildfire. a year later, wildfire is a small nook on the web about healthly living, finding stability, and a place for encouragement. But most importantly, it is the idea that sometimes God uses destruction to makeus fireproof. Through Wildfire, I hope to share real moments, failures, triumphs, and rawness. I pray it is a place Christians, especially women, can come and know that God still has their back, even in the midst of disaster. I desire for the words written in this blog to give you hope when you are down, conviction when there is pride, and serve as a reminder that you are not alone in the struggles you face</h2></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/wildfire/what-is-wildfire/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">5c0a9928-15fc-4176-8948-2b6ad405176a</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2016 02:08:16 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Fire—a destructive and terrorizing force. Even more terrorizing than this force, is this force without bounds, with no limits or restrictions—wild.Though we have been taught to mourn the ground zero left behind from a wildfire, nature knows that its destruction has purpose: through ruin, new life can grow. All that was old in the previously strangled forest is broken down to its smallest form, soaked and sown into the soil, then stronger, fire-resistant vegetation rises from the ashes of its past. To the unconnected, wildfire is devastating. Yet to those who seek the depths of destruction’s meaning, wildfire is the rebirth of all things beautiful. To become fire-proof, the old must die, the ashes must nurture the soil, and life must be born again.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/wildfire/firea-destructive-and-terrorizing-force-even-more-terroriz/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">21ce1d80-aee4-4167-a1f1-3921d48393c6</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2016 01:47:10 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>